Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Audiovisual materials, 1970-2014; 6; 37.88 linear feet (55 boxes)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 157 158 159 J1/92 65 347 758, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_19 (Reel 3, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Rev Key J1/97 22 21 152 785, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_20 (Reel 3, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 83/10 92 99 J1/96 27 28 293 090, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_21 (Reel 3, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/92 64 484 900, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_22 (Reel 3, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Vinh Linh Sync Outs Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_120 (Reel 30, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trims, FF0000, Mr. Diet & Heroine in red, Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_121 (Reel 30, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_122 (Reel 30, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numer. Trims FF0000 HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_281 (Reel 31, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Vinh Linh Sync Outs ADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_282 (Reel 31, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_283 (Reel 31, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Arthur Miller SYNC PIX HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_170 (Reel 32, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Arthur Miller MOS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_171 (Reel 32, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: tails boats from head of C-5, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_174 (Reel 33, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS-Actress/Jane, Tail CR: "Z"52, Junk, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_175 (Reel 33, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Tails W46 Heads-dark, I.J., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_176 (Reel 33, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Jane speaks to filmmaker audience, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_177 (Reel 33, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: PRTG Press, Actress Hanoi, Last Day, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_178 (Reel 33, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Salt workers/numericised trims PIX-Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_223 (Reel 34, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trim MOS Salt HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_224 (Reel 34, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised MOS Trims, HDS AC 0000, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_193 (Reel 35, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi-April 1-3, Deplaning w/ Tra Siong +Babies-street scenes-by lake-PRG Embassy AB 0000, MOS-I 1 Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_194 (Reel 35, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi-April 3-Schools-MOS I 2, AC 0000, Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_195 (Reel 35, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: SR 2- Le Duc Tho, Wild Sound #1, Insert Head, Interview R-1, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_329 (Reel 36, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Tail S-20 Le Duc Tho, CR P-30, Interview R-1, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_330 (Reel 36, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho Fast! S.R. 1 N.G., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_331 (Reel 36, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Wild SND A Head, Le Duc Tho SR-21 (From Tail of Interview R-2), approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_332 (Reel 36, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: S1 tail, replaced by S-20-Too fast!, S-1, N.G., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_333 (Reel 36, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Arthur Miller-wild sound tails, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_273 (Reel 37, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: S24 After Salt workers, Jane sings, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_274 (Reel 37, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Gerry Jacobson, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_275 (Reel 37, Drawer 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numer. Trim, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_237 (Reel 38, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_238 (Reel 38, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Sync + Mos pic for which ST is probably too fast, HEAD, Woman reads poen-exit village-Tank, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_239 (Reel 38, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Thanh Hoa-Bicycle Factory-Pot Factory-Walking shots-kids-Man w bike-leaving-country road, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_232 (Reel 39, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Road + Trees BA0000, Numericised Trims Thanh Hoa HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_233 (Reel 39, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Binoculars lifts from cup MOS HDS, binoc replaced, sargon flag etc binoc., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_234 (Reel 39, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: BA0000 MOS Bicycle Factory TRIMS Thanh Hoa HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_235 (Reel 39, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 280-102 R1, 1972 July 26; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_258 (Reel 4, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 280-102 R2, 1972 July 26; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_259 (Reel 4, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Thanh Hoa-Bicycle Factory-Pot Factory-Man w Bike III W.S. HEAD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_369 (Reel 40, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: WS Bike Factory Thanh Hoa HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_370 (Reel 40, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi-reconstruction/movie studio-printshop WS HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_357 (Reel 41, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_358 (Reel 41, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Man in hat Aitu-foll. 1st sync take, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_348 (Reel 42, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: WS-Arun Defeater/Camloc + Aitu Heads; goes w/ y51, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_349 (Reel 42, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Wild sound trims Binoc, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_351 (Reel 42, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Binocular scene; the bridge is destroyed, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_352 (Reel 42, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Ho Chi Minh song, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_315 (Reel 43, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: WS 2 old viets/Buddhist Heads Trim, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_316 (Reel 43, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Vinh Linh - 70 yr old man/bulldozers/heroine in red/pepper patch/on stage singing (heads), WS Heads XI & XII, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_317 (Reel 43, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Monk interview/children singing/2 old viets WS Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_409 (Reel 43, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_198 (Reel 44, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_199 (Reel 44, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Stock for Cultural Performances, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_90 (Reel 45, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Stock w/ white streaks?, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_91 (Reel 45, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: SWED wreckage, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_92 (Reel 45, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Swede Stock footage cut, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_93 (Reel 45, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Swedish Reconstruction, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_94 (Reel 45, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Bridge, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_95 (Reel 45, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Swedish-woman at machine gun, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_96 (Reel 45, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Swede house build, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_97 (Reel 45, Item 8)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Swed. School & thatch, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_98 (Reel 45, Item 9)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Market, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_99 (Reel 45, Item 10)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_100 (Reel 45, Item 11)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Dong Ha Truck, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_101 (Reel 45, Item 12)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 2 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) FondaFilm_102 (Reel 45, Item 13)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised Trim, 70 yr. old man, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_293 (Reel 46, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised trims FF000 TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_294 (Reel 46, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Vinh Linh-70 yr old man/, Sync Outs TRK Heads, 70 yr. old man sync outs, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_295 (Reel 46, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Vinh Linh-70 yr. old man/Sync outs pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_135 (Reel 47, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trim 70 yr. old man, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_136 (Reel 47, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trim MOS Mrs. Chi, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_244 (Reel 48, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Salt num. trims, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_245 (Reel 48, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Boat Ride, num. trims, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_246 (Reel 48, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Beach, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_247 (Reel 48, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: River N.G., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_248 (Reel 48, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Old Viet-sitting on boat, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_249 (Reel 48, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Xercises, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_359 (Reel 49, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised trims AA 0000 HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_360 (Reel 49, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Xercises, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_361 (Reel 49, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: AA sync outs, TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_362 (Reel 49, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_363 (Reel 49, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Binoculars HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_253 (Reel 5, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: ARUN Defector/MOS Camloc + Aitu HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_254 (Reel 5, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: RU-Cam Loc + Vicinity MOS Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_255 (Reel 5, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: AA sync outs, Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_219 (Reel 50, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Xercises, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_220 (Reel 50, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trims AA 0000 PIX Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_221 (Reel 50, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_222 (Reel 50, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Xercises, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_263 (Reel 50, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Mrs. Chi, Numericised trims, PIX Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_251 (Reel 51, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Mrs. Chi Sync outs, PIX Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_252 (Reel 51, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised trims Mrs. Chi TRK HEAD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_387 (Reel 52, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Mrs. Chi Sync Outs, TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_388 (Reel 52, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Quoc's trous & Chi, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_389 (Reel 52, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Translation-lifts from cut, HEADS, Mrs. Chi, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_390 (Reel 52, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Dong Ha Hosp. Trial WS Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_373 (Reel 53, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Dong Ha Hosp WS TRIMS HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_374 (Reel 53, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: [num]ericised [tri]ms Mr. Nam HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_375 (Reel 53, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Mine victim DA 0000, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_376 (Reel 53, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trims, MOS DA Dong Ha driving, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_150 (Reel 54, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Dong Ha Hospital MOS Heads VII + VIII, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_159 (Reel 54, Item 10)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trims MOS, Mr. Nam HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_151 (Reel 54, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Tail-Not Useful Hosp MOS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_152 (Reel 54, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Dong Ha Hosp. Trims HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_153 (Reel 54, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Trial, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_154 (Reel 54, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Mr. Nam MOS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_155 (Reel 54, Reel 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Mine Victim HDS DA0000, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_156 (Reel 54, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Pt 1 [woman symbol] MD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_157 (Reel 54, Item 8)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Trial MOS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_158 (Reel 54, Item 9)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: More perf., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_129 (Reel 55, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Audience cut-aways for cultural performance, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_130 (Reel 55, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: On Stage, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_131 (Reel 55, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, 5/3EF58, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_132 (Reel 55, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Trims from final cut Cult. Perf., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_287 (Reel 56, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Cult. Perf. End, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_288 (Reel 56, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Verse one Performance, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_289 (Reel 56, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Other songs. Cultural perf., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_290 (Reel 56, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Quoc, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_291 (Reel 56, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Tails-Quoc Jane - cutaway MOS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_209 (Reel 57, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: End, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_210 (Reel 57, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi SYNC OUTS HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_339 (Reel 58, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: TRA Giong Vo Trans, Numericised trims, AA 5000, TRK HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_342 (Reel 58, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Remaining Poem-cult., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_345 (Reel 59, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_346 (Reel 59, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: how old is he sync, WS Salt worker trims, heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_391 (Reel 6, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: see wild sound → numericised trims, Salt workers TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_392 (Reel 6, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Salt →, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_393 (Reel 6, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: WS Cua Viet & SALTVI; wild AA- before Mrs. Chi's 1st sync take, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_394 (Reel 6, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: WS trims Mmc Chi HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_395 (Reel 6, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: They leveled the ground trans., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_396 (Reel 6, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: dd salt wavah (old salt), approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_397 (Reel 6, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Salt workers WS Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_398 (Reel 6, Item 8)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi Montage trims DA, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_182 (Reel 60, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trim, Hanoi + Viea, JA 5000 Heads; Hanoi, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_183 (Reel 60, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS AA + AD, Numericised Trims, Hanoi Montage, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_184 (Reel 60, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Movie Studio, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_185 (Reel 60, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Numericised Trims JA, Hanoi Montage, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_186 (Reel 60, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Numericised trims, AC Hanoi Montage, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_187 (Reel 60, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS for Hanoi Montage HD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_188 (Reel 60, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_189 {rec'd - Part 2} (Reel 60, Item 8)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Numericised trims, AB, Hanoi Montage, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_191 (Reel 60, Item 9)